<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<texte>

	<text name="impressum">
	<![CDATA[
PUBLISHER:

extra toxic GmbH & Co. KG
Hanauer Landstraße 196a
60314 Frankfurt
phone: +49 (0)69 / 48 44 00 - 40
fax: +49 (0)69 / 48 44 00 - 39
email: <a href="mailto:info@extratoxic.com"><u>info@extratoxic.com</u></a>
web: <a href="http://www.extratoxic.com" target="_blank"><u>www.extratoxic.com</u></a>

CEOs: Christiane Fritsch, Bogac Sariaydin, Steve Welz
registration office: Amtsgericht Frankfurt am Main
registration #: HRA 42957

liable associate: extra toxic Verwaltungsgesellschaft mbH
partners: Christiane Fritsch, Bogac Sariaydin, Steve Welz
registration office: Amtsgericht Frankfurt am Main
registration #: HRB 76625

VAT #: DE 814546108

DISCLAIMER:

We of course are keen to provide you only with complete, true and up-to-date information on our web sites. We are not liable for any mistakes though, should they unintentionally occur.

We are not responsible for the content of off-site web sites or any other web sites linked or linking to our web sites. The copyrights for and the responsibility concerning the content of those off-site web sites belong to their owner exclusively.

To use our web site you need the Flash Player 8 Plugin or higher.

PRIVACY:

extra toxic GmbH & Co. KG and Nintendo recognise the importance of your privacy. All information and data that you may provide - subject to your instructions to the contrary - will be retained and disclosed only in accordance with applicable national data protection laws and regulations and in any event only to the degree necessary to efficiently process your specific request. extra toxic GmbH & Co. KG and Nintendo will not collect your personal data without your consent. It is entirely your decision as to whether you would like to disclose your individually identifiable information. Your personal data will be stored securely and will not be passed to any third party or company.

COPYRIGHT:

All content on this web site, including articles, artwork, screen shots, graphics, logos, digital downloads and other files, is the property of <a href="http://www.nintendo-europe.com/NOE/fr/FR/copyright/index.jsp" target="_blank"><u>Nintendo</u></a> and extra toxic GmbH & Co. KG, unless owned by a third party, and is protected by German and international copyright, trademark and other intellectual property laws. Trademarks and copyrights for third-party content are owned by the companies that market or license those products.

Complete or partial reproduction, publishing, transfer (electronically or in other ways), modification, and using of our web sites and content for public or commercial purposes is prohibited withour prior written approval. Of course we are happy about references to our web site and insofar ask for notification.

CREDITS:

Original Music & SFX by:
Fabian Del Priore
<a href="http://www.sonicminds.de" target="_blank"><u>www.sonicminds.de</u></a>
A division of Dynamedion

Servers and Loadbalancing powered by:
<a href="http://www.ping247.de" target="_blank"><u>Ping247</u></a>
Carsten Urbanski
	]]>
	</text>

</texte>